[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "Have you ever seen one quite that candid and raw?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "RB", "WDT", "VBD", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dan"]}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "VB", "POS", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "What do you want Barack Obama now to really achieve that will be his legacy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Well, first of all, I think that we all think of and we talk about the president's coolness, and with due respect to Dan, whom I enormously admire, let's not confuse composure with coolness.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Well, they failed and there is a certain liberation that comes with being re-elected, isn't there, an empowerment that says OK, well, stuff you, I'm back for four years and I'm going to make things happen now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Well, there is that, but we need to keep in mind that second terms for presidents generally speaking historically have not turned out that well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Tim Pawlenty, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "I'm doing well, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tim Pawlenty"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Why was that belief so built on sand, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Well, of course, election results are a little like post-modern art.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "How long can the Republicans, led by the Grover Norquist gang, sustain a position of there is zero movement or flexibility for any increased taxation when most Americans think it's perfectly reasonable given there's a $16 trillion debt that the wealthiest should pay more tax?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "WRB", "JJS", "NNPS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "$", "CD", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, let's give some examples, Piers, of where the two sides could come together.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$16 trillion"], "PERSON": ["Grover Norquist"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "What is the difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "I think it's fair to say, Piers, that the Republicans aren't going to raise tax rates but they are willing to look at raising some revenues along the lines that I've described and if you get to the same result, I think that's a good step forward in the interest of trying to find a bipartisan solution.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "What's the matter with you, man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I didn't say I wasn't impressed by them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Did you think Mitt Romney could ever do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "I definitely think Mitt Romney could do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Do you understand why so many women did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "You know, I think this is an election about the economy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Then he had to slowly back pedal again, by which time really, in terms of principle, he's toast, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "WDT", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Well, I think that we may be missing something.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "So Brian, why is this a good thing then, to legalize cannabis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brian"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Kevin Sabet, why is it a terrible idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Well, I think legalization is really an extreme answer.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kevin Sabet"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "If you overdo alcohol, if you're a young person, for example?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "I think they're very different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 412, "question": "They would suffer similar issues, wouldn't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Some similar --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Isn't that the argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "That's absolutely true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Isn't it a waste of law enforcement finances and resources?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Well, first of all, I'm not saying to jail marijuana users.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "What were the feelings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "It was certainly a little stressful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "What did you mean by that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "I mean it's time to move on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Do you think now is the time, now that he has got another four-year term, to really do something really meaningful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Well, he certainly has a lot on his plate, you know, with the economy and the situation we have, the approaching fiscal cliff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]